

704 Sky Court Palace Ryogoku, Ryogoku 3-16-6, Sumida-ku, Tokyo 130-0026 080-9447-0608 barnes.kai@gmail.com github.com/kaibarnes KaiBarnes.com

I am a Marketing and Advertising graduate from the UK. I studied Japanese and passed N2 of the JLPT after arriving in Japan. I am now studying front-end web development and joining a range of meetups around Tokyo to further my skills. I am looking for a front-end developer position to begin my career.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript **CSS Frameworks:** Bootstrap, Foundation

Javascript Frameworks & Libraries: ¡Query, React, React Native, Meteor

Content Management: Wordpress **Databases:** MongoDB, Firebase

Testing: Jest, Expect

Recent Projects

Party Planner - http://party-planner.surge.sh/

A site I made using React and Firebase to plan parties with coworkers by showing venue suggestions and keeping a total of the number of votes.

Candy Marche - http://www.candymarche.com/

A freelance project using PHP. Worked together with a designer and the project leader.

Tap Adventure game- https://github.com/kaibarnes/TapAdventure

A tap based game I developed to test the concept and how to apply it to React Native development.

Shinpuru Japanese Dictionary- https://github.com/kaibarnes/Shinpuru

A Japanese dictionary app I developed using React Native. Translates English vocabulary using an API and gives an option to save favorite translations locally

Career History

Candymarche.com Freelance Project

10/2017

- Hired to develop a site using PHP
- Worked from Photoshop designs and a style guide, and consulted with a the designer

English Instructor Gaba Corporation – Tokyo, Japan

11/2014 to Present

- Teaching English in corporate head offices and shopping mall eikaiwa
- Working together with Japanese staff to conduct first meetings with potential new clients

Intern 12/2011 to 05/2012

Skull and Bones Boys Club Clothing Company - Sheffield, United Kingdom

Promoted new products at events and on social media

Education

Kai Japanese Language School - Tokyo, Japan

09/2012 to 09/2014

• Translated for Nihon Kougakuin College during their summer course

BA (Honours) Marketing and Advertising Sheffield Hallam University – Sheffield, United Kingdom

09/2009 to 07/2012

- Studied a wide range of subjects including Customer Psychology, Product Design and Sales Skills
- Emphasis on teamwork and presentation skills

Other

JLPT N2 Engineer/Specialist in Humanities/International Services Visa 08/2014 11/2015 to 11/2018